dailysignal.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy - The Daily Signal

## The Daily Signal’s Privacy Policy

Your privacy on the Internet is important to us. As part of the operation and customization feature of The Daily Signal’s web site (“DailySignal.com”), we gather certain types of information from users, and we would like to explain the types of information we gather, what we do with them, and how to correct or change the information. The privacy policies for DailySignal.com also apply to the Heritage Insights Panel.

## Information Collected By DailySignal.com

DailySignal.com collects two types of information from users: personal data such as zip code, email address and demographic information; and aggregated data such as information about traffic patterns on DailySignal.com (for example, how many users log on to DailySignal.com on a daily basis).

## Aggregated Information

Aggregated information, such as which pages users visit, is collected through various means. One of these ways is through an IP address, a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that “serve up” Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you request a page from DailySignal.com, our servers log your IP address. DailySignal.com does not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, so although your session will be logged, your session will remain anonymous to us. DailySignal.com collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration only.

## Use of Cookies

DailySignal.com uses cookies to automate the process of logging on to certain areas of the site. The DailySignal.com cookie is a small data file stored on your computer that contains a single, randomly assigned user ID number. By recognizing this ID number, DailySignal.com can automatically provide you with the personalized content for which you requested. Cookies can neither read any other files on your computer, nor damage your computer. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you’d prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent.

## Use of Information Collected by DailySignal.com

DailySignal.com uses both the personal and aggregated information we collect for multiple purposes. The information is used to improve the content of the site, to customize the content and/or layout of the site for each individual user, target promotions on other sites and if requested, to provide information services by email to the user. After registration, users will receive a single email message confirming registration. The Daily Signal will never disclose your personally identifiable information to a third party outside the Heritage family of organizations unless required to do so by court order, law or governmental agency.

## Information Security at DailySignal.com

Heritage Foundation employees understand the need for user privacy and access to user data is strictly limited and can only be accessed by specific individuals who have the necessary username and password combination.

## Children and Privacy

The Daily Signal encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children. In general, DailySignal.com will not contain content that is reasonably considered unsuitable for children.

## Links to Other Sites

It is important to note that DailySignal.com contains links to sites other than DailySignal.com, and that those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as DailySignal.com. For instance, a link in the “External Resources” section of DailySignal.com will take you away from DailySignal.com to an entirely different site.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

The Daily Signal reserves the right to change the policy on use of information collected. Any changes in policy will be noted in a revised privacy policy statement and will be posted at least 30 days prior to implementation. You may direct any privacy policy questions to [info@heritage.org](mailto:info@heritage.org).
